# **Emrullah Yaprak**

- Dublin, Ireland
- **\** +353830854827
- @ yaprakemrullah22@gmail.com
- emrullahyaprak.com
- github.com/eyaprak
- www.linkedin.com/in/emrullah-yaprak/

# **SUMMARY**

I am currently living in Dublin, Ireland. I'm a student at an English school located in Dublin, and I am studying there every day until 12.30 p.m and I have a Stamp 1 visa type. So I can only work for 20 hours each week. I have more than 5 years of experience in Web Development. I used to develop applications with PHP, Flutter, Oracle PL/SQL, Wordpress etc. I have been working with React.js, Next.js, Node.js, MongoDB and many other technologies until December 2020. During this time, I have created projects that can be viewed in my portfolio website. One of them, developed using Flutter and published it on Google Play.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

December 2020-Current

### **FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER**

- **■** FREELANCER
- Dublin, Ireland
- I have been working with Node.js, Express.js, React.js, Next.js, MongoDB, Tailwindcss, MaterialUI, Redux and many other technologies until December 2020. In this process, I have created many projects that can be viewed in the my portfolio website.

June 2019-December 2020

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

- **B** GENEX SOFTWARE INC
- Istanbul, Turkey
- Used HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, NODE.JS and created responsive pages in Oracle Apex.
- · Used Node.js to got datas from API in Oracle Apex and created few IG with this data.
- Designed application framework and developed Oracle APEX Application.
- Converted Oracle Forms pages to Oracle Apex pages.
- Prepare plugins on the Oracle Apex system.
- Worked with Sql Developer managed data and tables.
- Created various DML and DDL statements using PL/SQL and SQL.
- Installed and updated Oracle Apex Dashboard product on clients.
- · Worked closely with clients to establish problem specifications and system designs.
- Used Wordpress system to build websites.
- Managed and kept the Wordpress website of the company updated.

- Inserted products on websites and managed products price, description and other requirements.
- Shared products on market places and kept them up-to-date.

November 2016-March 2017

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

- **E** COŞKUN YAYINCILIK INC
- Istanbul, Turkey
- Used HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT and PHP programing languages.
- · Used Wordpress system to build websites.
- · Managed and kept the Wordpress website of the company updated.
- Inserted products on websites and managed products price, description and other requirements.
- Shared products on market places and kept them up-to-date.

June 2016-August 2016

### **INTERNSHIP**

- **MERCEDES BENZ TURK INC**
- Istanbul, Turkey
- I saw an internship for 60 working days in the human resources department at Mercedes-Benz Türk A.Ş.

July 2014-September 2014

### Sales Manager

- **B** AYFA PRESS & BROADCAST DISTRIBUTION INC
- Istanbul, Turkey

## **EDUCATION**

2015-2019

# **Bachelor's in COMPUTER ENGINEERING**

- Duzce University
- O Düzce, Turkey

Bachelor's in COMPUTER ENGINEERING Duzce University

September 2015 to June 2019

COMPUTER ENGINEERING

#### **SKILLS**

API HTML Javascript Javascript Frameworks and Libraries Node.JS React PHP

Software Engineer Structured Software Development DDL Oracle Oracle Forms PL/SQL SQL CSS APEX Mongodb Wordpress Sales Manager

# **LANGUAGES**

English - Intermediate Turkish - Fluent

# **WORK AUTHORISATION**

I am authorised to work in the following countries:

Ireland